{
    "subject": "Ann_Sothern",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Robert_Sterling",
    "human_readable": "Ann Sothern is married to Robert Sterling.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9882586002349854,
            "question": "Is Robert Sterling married to Ann Sothern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9856443405151367,
            "question": "Is Robert Sterling's wife Ann Sothern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9141209125518799,
            "question": "Who are Ann Sothern and Robert Sterling in a relationship with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9004089832305908,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ann Sothern and Robert Sterling?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8785538673400879,
            "question": "Who is Ann Sothern married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8272661566734314,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Ann Sothern."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7482507824897766,
            "question": "What can we say about Ann Sothern and Robert Sterling's relationship status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6064766645431519,
            "question": "What is the name of Ann Sothern's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5846107006072998,
            "question": "To whom is Ann Sothern legally bound?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5115967392921448,
            "question": "Who shares a marital bond with Ann Sothern?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ann Sothern is married to Robert Sterling.",
            "html": "yago_4668_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Ann Sothern legally bound?",
            "html": "yago_4668_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ann Sothern's husband?",
            "html": "yago_4668_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we say about Ann Sothern and Robert Sterling's relationship status?",
            "html": "yago_4668_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4668_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Robert Sterling and Ann Sothern were married from 1943 to 1949, which supports the statement that Ann Sothern was married to Robert Sterling."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}